Hi! I’m Tripat Sandhu and I’m
a fourth-year student studying
Criminal Justice, I also
play on the UFV women's soccer team.
One of the reasons I chose to study and play
at UFV is because of the excellent facilities
at the UFV Athletic Center and top
notch coaching and support for thirteen Cascade
varsity teams. I also really value the
friendships I make on and off the field.
I love the energy when this twenty one thousand
five hundred square foot
gymnasium is packed on game day
with students screaming, “Go Cascades Go!”
I can't wait till we play again.
Building E also home to UFV's Campus Recreation,
which offers intramural sports and fitness
classes to the UFV community.
During covid restrictions
you can stay fit and workout with your friends
through online classes offered
through UFV's campus rec.
That's a really important part of
practicing wellness during the pandemic.
I hope you enjoyed my tour.
If you're an athlete,
consider becoming a Cascade like me.
See you at the gym.