Hi there, my name is Neeraj Kumar and I study Computer Information Systems Diploma here
at University of the Fraser Valley. Today,
I am going to show you some of UFV's learning locations.
Now, we are in the library. This bright and
beautiful space is where you can do academic research and work on your own or with classmates.
Right now, you can go online to sign-out study
resources using the library's "select and
collect" curbside pick-up service. The library
will even mail you the books and other resources if you are not living in the Fraser Valley
this semester. Something, I personally love about the library is their private study rooms
which you can book online and go with other classmates or go by your own. This is a computer
lab. It's fully equipped with all the IT essentials you will need to complete any coursework.
During Covid-19, you can log into the computer lab from home. It's super easy, I do like
10 times a day.
Thanks for coming on my tour of Building G. Hope to see you at UFV next semester.