Hi. I’m Alec, a fourth year studying Philosophy here at the University of the Fraser Valley.
When I am not in class, you can find me right here in Building S. Let me show you around.
First stop is the UFV Career Centre. Here, you can book a virtual session
with a Career Coach to get help with your resume and tips on how to land that perfect job!
Next, is the Student Union Society or “SUS”. This student-run organization advocates for
things like the U-Pass program and student health and dental plans. They also contribute to the
popular SUS peer tutoring program - a great resource to help boost your GPA.
Over here, we have the Student Life Department who provide peer mentorship and leadership development.
They also connect students with clubs and associations that match their interests.
With a wide range of options, from Amnesty International to the
Pen and Paper Tabletop Club
to the UFV Theatre Association, I’m sure there’s a club or association you’ll want to get involved in!
Finally, when you have some downtime, grab a coffee or lunch here at the student-run Fair Grounds
or Streats. You haven’t lived until you’ve had the tacos!  The best part of the university is getting
the full campus experience. So make sure to get involved and make the most of all the opportunities.